{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What is part of a database that holds only one type of information?",
            "options": [
                "Report",
                "Field",
                "Record",
                "File"
            ],
            "ans": "Field"
        },
        {
            "question": "'OS' computer abbreviation usually means?",
            "options": [
                "Order of Significance ",
                "Open Software",
                "Operating System",
                "Optical Sensor"
            ],
            "ans": "Operating System"
        },
        {
            "question": "'.MOV' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
            "options": [
                "Image file",
                "Animation/movie file",
                "Audio file",
                "MS Office document"
            ],
            "ans": "Animation/movie file"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is a type of Electrically-Erasable Programmable Read-Only Memory?",
            "options": [
                "Flash",
                "Flange",
                "Fury",
                "FRAM"
            ],
            "ans": "Flash"
        },
        {
            "question": "'.MPG' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
            "options": [
                "WordPerfect Document file",
                "MS Office document",
                "Animation/movie file",
                "Image file"
            ],
            "ans": "Animation/movie file"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who developed Yahoo?",
            "options": [
                "Dennis Ritchie,Ken Thompson",
                "David Filo,Jerry Yang",
                "Vint Cerf,Robert Kahn",
                "Steve Case,Jeff Bezos"
            ],
            "ans": "David Filo,Jerry Yang"
        },
        {
            "question": "The most common format for a home video recorder is VHS. VHS stands for...?",
            "options": [
                "Video Home System",
                "Very high speed",
                "Video horizontal standard",
                "Voltage house standard"
            ],
            "ans": "Video Home System"
        },
        {
            "question": "'DB' computer abbreviation usually means?",
            "options": [
                "Database",
                "Double Byte",
                "Data Block",
                "Driver Boot"
            ],
            "ans": "Database"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who co-founded Hotmail in 1996 and then sold the company to Microsoft?",
            "options": [
                "Shawn Fanning",
                "Ada Byron Lovelace",
                "Sabeer Bhatia",
                "Ray Tomlinson"
            ],
            "ans": "Sabeer Bhatia"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the UK, what type of installation requires a fireman's switch?",
            "options": [
                "Neon Lighting",
                "High Pressure Sodium Lighting",
                "Water Features",
                "Hotel Rooms"
            ],
            "ans": "Neon Lighting"
        }
    ]
}